<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<!--
	New Artefacts
-->

<string_table>
	<string id="st_af_cocoon_name">
		<text>Cocoon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cocoon_descr">
		<text>Formation of thermal nature. Significantly reduces the weight of the transported cargo, for which it is valued by stalkers. It also has some radioprotective effect.
		\n \nRadiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.</text>
		 
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cell_name">
		<text>Cell</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_cell_descr">
		<text>An artefact of gravity breed. Generates a local gravitational field, which significantly reduces the impact of the force of attraction, and also to some extent levels the physical impact of external forces. It is quite rare, but still occurs in places of abnormal gravitational activity.
		\n \nRadiation output is high on the artefact radiation scale.</text>
		 
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fountain_name">
		<text>Fountain</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fountain_descr">
		<text>Gravitational anomalous formation. The "fountain" prevents objects from moving in a small area around it. According to scientists, this is due to the unusual gravitational field generated by the artefact. Interestingly, the effect of an artefact is all the more noticeable the greater the speed of a moving object that falls within its area of action; this property is what prompted stalkers to use the artefact as a protective element.
		\n \nRadiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_spaika_name">
		<text>Spike</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_spaika_descr">
		<text>It looks like a fossilized formation. It is an artefact of thermal breed. Like the Fountain artefact, it affects objects moving in its field, but it is more pronounced, which is why it is of particular interest to scientists.
		\n \nRadiation output is average on the artefact radiation scale.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_signet_name">
		<text>Signet</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_signet_descr">
		<text>Stalkers also call this artefact "Amulet". The properties of this artefact are the ability to create a powerful gravitational field in a small radius, which reduces the kinetic energy of any moving objects that fall within its area of action. Many also believe that it brings good luck.
		\n \nRadiation output is high on the artefact radiation scale.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_repei_name">
		<text>Thistle</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_repei_descr">
		<text>It is often caused by thermal anomalies. It has quite valuable properties for removing radiation from the host's body, as well as slightly reducing the impact of it. Due to its gravitational radiation, it has the ability to lighten the weight of the backpack, making it quite attractive prey for many novice stalkers.
		\n \nNot radioactive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_bat_name">
		<text>Bat</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_bat_descr">
		<text>Very beautiful anomalous formation. In terms of magnetic properties, it is similar to ultra-high - density metals. However, it has a relatively low specific mass of the substance. Creates a fairly powerful gravitational field. It also has a weak field that partially blocks psi waves. It is considered rare due to the complexity of detection, although it is formed quite often. Surprisingly, the artefact is completely non-radioactive.
		\n \nNot radioactive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_sun_name">
		<text>Sun</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_sun_descr">
		<text>Quite a rare specimen, which is very much appreciated by collectors. Abnormal formation of a symbiosis of gravitational and thermal anomalies. Presumably, an alloy of artefacts "Sandstone" and "Gravi". Despite a number of useful characteristics, it is worth remembering that the "Sun" is an extremely radioactive artefact.
		\n \nRadiation output is high on the artefact radiation scale.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ear_name">
		<text>Heart</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ear_descr">
		<text>An artefact of a bizarre shape, the core of which resembles a human organ. It is difficult to say why this artefact got its name: because of its appearance or because of its excellent healing properties. But what is most surprising is that the "Heart" has absolutely atypical properties for products of gravitational anomalies, which once again indicates that a person is still very far from understanding the mechanisms operating in the Zone.
		\n \nNot radioactive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_chelust_name">
		<text>Chain</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_chelust_descr">
		<text>A very strange artefact. Starts generating a gravitational field if nothing comes into physical contact with it. But it is quite heavy, which significantly reduces the benefit of the field it creates. It does not protect against induced radiation, but it remove the dose already received very well.
		\n \nNot radioactive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_atom_name">
		<text>Atom</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_atom_descr">
		<text>An abnormal formation of rare beauty. Looks like an atom. However, in addition to its unusual appearance, it also has a number of valuable characteristics that have a beneficial effect on the host's body. Unless, of course, you take into account the rather strong radiation background. Emits a small amount of heat.
		\n \nRadiation output is high on the artefact radiation scale.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_lighthouse_name">
		<text>Beacon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_lighthouse_descr">
		<text>A super-dense clot of substance. It has a weak but constant stimulating effect on the respiratory system. When exposed to a radioactive environment, it can emit a cloud of colorless gas that has sufficiently strong neutralizing properties. However, this same gas can have a negative impact on the regenerative abilities of living organisms, so thoughtlessly carrying this artefact can lead to serious health consequences and even death.
		\n \nNot radioactive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fire_loop_name">
		<text>Knot</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fire_loop_descr">
		<text>A necessary condition for generating this artefact is the impact and proximity of the thermal anomaly. It has a whimsical appearance, and is therefore valued by collectors. The ability to lower the temperature in a small radius makes it a good thermal protection element, and the property of accelerating blood clotting makes the "Loop" a good alternative to conventional hemostatic agents.
		\n \nRadiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_zhelch_name">
		<text>Scar</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_zhelch_descr">
		<text>The artefact has a calming effect on the human nervous system. It is also highly valued by jewelers. It has pronounced healing properties. It has a beneficial effect on the entire body as a whole. The absence of harmful radiation and the complexity of detection make this artefact particularly valuable.
		\n \nNot radioactive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_sandstone_name">
		<text>Sandstone</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_sandstone_descr">
		<text>An artefact that is formed in thermally unsafe areas. A powerful repairer of organic tissues. In combination with the stabilizing effect of the respiratory system, it enhances the biosynthesis of RNA, functional and enzymatic cell elements, including components of cell membranes, and also stimulates DNA reduplication and cell division. Contains a small amount of pure gold.
		\n \nRadiation output is high on the artefact radiation scale.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_kislushka_name">
		<text>Sourpuss</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_kislushka_descr">
		<text>A hollow formation of a spherical shape, resembling transparent parchment. Covered with a layer of film, pleasant to the touch.  It has a faint emerald inner glow. It is popular among stalkers due to its ability to partially neutralize chemicals harmful to humans, as well as to stimulate the regenerative function of the body.
		\n \nRadiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_black_angel_name">
		<text>Black Angel</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_black_angel_descr">
		<text>A root-like artefact. When it does not come into physical contact with anything, it begins to hover above the surface. It has a fairly strong field that can block psi waves within a certain radius of itself. It repeatedly accelerates the regeneration of tissues and organs of living creatures, but if used incorrectly, the entire positive effect can come to naught due to the increased radiation background. Highly valued by collectors.
		\n \nRadiation output is high on the artefact radiation scale.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_grapes_name">
		<text>Grapes</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_grapes_descr">
		<text>A fused piece of greenish wood resin. As a result of various anomalous impacts and emissions, it has acquired powerful radio-absorbing properties. Its uniqueness lies not so much in the fact that it is a "black hole" for radionuclides, but in the ability to repeatedly accelerate the half-life of any isotopes. In other words, this is a real radiation utilizer.
		\n \nNot radioactive.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_skull_miser_name">
		<text>Miser's skull</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_skull_miser_descr">
		<text>Very light and fragile artefact. Contains a substance whose properties can have a beneficial effect on the body. According to the observations of scientists, it is absolutely not dangerous, which makes it attractive for both stalkers and wealthy customers outside the zone.
		\n \nNot radioactive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_star_phantom_name">
		<text>Phantom star</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_star_phantom_descr">
		<text>Abnormal formation, which is a plasma substance in a transparent pulsating shell. Generates a weak gravitational field. Creates a unique healing effect on the human body, and is also able to remove radiation. Because of the high cost, it is the subject of Stalker hunting.
		\n \nNot radioactive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_medallion_name">
		<text>Medal</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_medallion_descr">
		<text>It is a small diameter Hoop with four impaled parts of a streamlined triangular shape, which have two pairs of opposite charges that randomly change their location within the structure. The properties of this artefact can be described as protective. It has two oppositely charged poles, which, when interacting, create a spatial inhomogeneity. The relative hardness of such a "Coulomb" is provided by compounds that absorb the energy of all external anomalous influences. Very much valued by collectors.
		\n \nRadiation output is average on the artefact radiation scale.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_peas_name">
		<text>Moon</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_peas_descr">
		<text>A Crescent-shaped artefact. Generates weak and dim light. It has quite strange properties. On the one hand, it repeatedly accelerates tissue regeneration, on the other - prevents blood clotting in open wounds. Among stalkers, there are known cases of death due to acquired hemophilia caused by its action, for which the artefact has gained a very bad reputation, especially in novice circles. However, experienced stalkers quickly realized that the negative effects can be compensated by other artefacts with hemostatic properties or the timely use of necessary medications.
		\n \nRadiation output is average on the artefact radiation scale.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_generator_name">
		<text>Generator</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_generator_descr">
		<text>The artefact generates weak electric currents and an electromagnetic field. It is a source of energy, and therefore very much appreciated outside the perimeter of the zone. It also has a stimulating effect on the muscular system, increasing its performance and reducing the fatigue threshold.
		\n \nRadiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_ball_name">
		<text>Ball</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_ball_descr">
		<text>Very mobile and bouncy artefact. There is no exact data on the conditions under which this spherical artefact is formed, which is why it got its name, but practice shows that it can most often be found in places of increased thermal activity. It has the property of redistributing kinetic energy, reducing the effects of bumps and falls. It is also able to partially neutralize the negative effects of psi radiation, even with very long-term exposure to humans. Like many artefacts of thermal anomalies, gives the bearer protection from exposure to high temperatures, though minimal.
		\n \nRadiation output is low on the artefact radiation scale.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_fonar_name">
		<text>Lamp</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_fonar_descr">
		<text>An artefact of an electric breed. It emits a weak stream of energy and glows. It is of some interest to science, as it releases anti-gravitational energy. Interesting for collectors.
		\n \nNot radioactive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_tapeworm_name">
		<text>Tapeworm</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_tapeworm_descr">
		<text>In fact, it is pure silicon dioxide, if we take into account only the atomic mass of the substance. Has strange behavior. It differs from natural crystal not only in its rich vitriol hue, but also in its mechanical characteristics. Formed in clusters of "Electra" type anomalies, this quartz fragment has a complex system of internal currents with external dielectric properties.
		\n \nNot radioactive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_moh_name">
		<text>Moss</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_moh_descr">
		<text>An artefact of an electric breed. In a strange way, it combines the properties characteristic of the products of gravitational and electrical anomalies, although it is known for certain that it is generated exclusively in electric-type anomalies.
		\n \nNot radioactive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_serofim_name">
		<text>Seraphim</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_serofim_descr">
		<text>A rare artefact of electromagnetic nature. Generates short-term electrical impulses that have a beneficial effect on the body. Improves overall health, as well as cellular and tissue metabolism. According to its main characteristics, it is a double-acting metabolic corrector that promotes rapid recovery of the body. By stimulating the metabolism of various chemical groups, it accelerates the growth of muscle mass to a certain extent.
		\n \nRadiation output is high on the artefact radiation scale.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_elektron_name">
		<text>Electron</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_elektron_descr">
		<text>The artefact is a product of electrical anomalies. In comparison with many other artefacts, "Electron" can "boast" only the ability to quickly remove radiation from the body. However, its transportation is quite difficult due to the abnormally large mass. But it is this quality, as well as the complexity of detection, that makes this artefact especially valuable. Scientific laboratories pay good money for such samples.
		\n \nNot radioactive.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_kogot_name">
		<text>Claw</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_kogot_descr">
		<text>Beautiful glass-like formation of electrostatic anomalies. There is a considerable danger behind the external attractiveness: the artefact can cause significant harm to health, although it has excellent hemostatic properties.
		\n \nRadiation output is average on the artefact radiation scale.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_af_vaselisk_name">
		<text>Basilisk</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_vaselisk_descr">
		<text>One of the few artefacts in The zone that does a good job with all kinds of effects on its owner. There is a legend among stalkers that it can bring the dead back to life. Whether this is true or not, this artefact helps not to die in the most dangerous anomalous zones, even without proper equipment. Interestingly, it also removes radiation perfectly, but it is absolutely not radioactive.
		\n \nNot radioactive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_geliy_name">
		<text>Helium</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_geliy_descr">
		<text>Bright (in the literal sense of the word) representative of the electrostatic family of artefacts. It releases a gaseous substance that is rumored to have a beneficial effect on the body. Due to its high efficiency, it is in great demand.
		\n \nNot radioactive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gimlet_name">
		<text>Gimlet </text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_gimlet_descr">
		<text>The Cup-shaped petals of the artefact are sources of the release of a powerful gaseous stimulant. The effect of which is a positive change in the hormonal background.
		\n \nNot radioactive.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dragon_eye_name">
		<text>Dragon's eye</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_af_dragon_eye_descr">
		<text>The artefact is formed more often in fire anomalies and has the appearance of a reptilian eye. It significantly reduces the weight of the backpack, and also has good recovery characteristics. Slightly protects from fire, absorbing some of the heat. Due to its extreme rarity and high efficiency, it is in great demand.
		\n \nRadiation output is high on the artefact radiation scale.</text>
	</string>
	
	<string id="st_arty_save">
		<text>Eye of the Noosphere</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_arty_save_descr">
		<text>One of the most mysterious artefacts in the Zone, the Eye of the Noosphere can transport its wielder back in time, even to escape death. A tight squeeze of the artefact activates its ability, creating a restoration point to go back to on activation or death. Frequent use can cause the artefact to change colour, but if discharged too frequently it may cease to function altogether. The Eye gradually restores its power over time, supposedly being fuelled by the anomalous energy of the Zone.\n \n
		%c[ui_gray_2]PROPERTIES:\n
		%c[ui_white] • %c[0,255,215,0] superartefact</text>
	</string>
</string_table>
